TYRES SQUEAL
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
LAUGHTER
That's it, Pusface!
Jonny! Keep running!
Get off! What?
Pissface! Agh! Oh! Oh!
I did it! You weirdo.
Running all the way.
Water! Water, please?
Ugh! Please?
My champion!
Salt? You bloody arsehole!
It worked! It worked!
Jonathan!
Come in, Adam.
YOU... can piss off!
What...? Oi!
My little Bobble.
Running home to Mummy.
That was a killer. Classic.
Ow!
Mum! Come through, sweetie.
Dead.
HE CHORTLES
Here you are, darling.
Thirsty.
I bet you are. So brave.
So brave? So disgusting!
SNIFFS
Oh, he stinks.
Er, do you want me to rub my sweaty
groin juice all over your face?
You dare!
Boys! Ugh, groin juice?! Revolting!
TUTS
Oh, beef tonight.
Beef? Boom! Yes!
# Bring it on! #
And I thought maybe you were going
to ask your girlfriends over,
you know, the ones we've never met?
You thought wrong.
Very wrong.
Oh, it is Dad's birthday.
Where is the birthday boy... er,
man?
And what is this doing here?
Cos your not-mad father made me
take it all down.
Did he?He's been such a
misery guts all day.
I don't know what to do with him.
Push him off the roof?
LAUGHS
Finally.
Wait! Just a minute.
There, Bobble. Really?
Good boy.
Good dog. Pissface!
Oh, hello, Martin.
GRUNTS
Happy birthday, Dad.
Happy birthday.
Balls! Sorry? What? Balls!
Can you please stop saying "balls"
every time anyone wishes you
a happy birthday?! See?
Why are you dressed like a berk?
You are in a good mood, aren't you?
Martin, you know
Adam was running here tonight.
Why were you running again?
Cos he's a tit. Groin juice?
Don't you dare!
Don't you remember?
For his training.
The race, remember? Sunday?
What? Oh, yeah. The marathon.
It's not a marathon. Really?
You're running a marathon, aren't
you? Very good.
You know it's not a marathon.
Sorry. Half marathon. Keep going.
You don't mean
quarter marathon, do you?
Stop it, Jonny. It's not a quarter
marathon, is it?
It's a half marathon. Mum, I told
you, it's a quarter marathon.
That's what I've been training for
a quarter marathon.
Quarter marathon? Does that even
exist?
I bet you couldn't run a quarter
marathon.
Course I could. What, is it? A mile?
Er, 6.5 miles.
6.55 miles.
Human calculator. Ugh! I need more
water. Allow me. Er, no thanks!
Boys, behave!
Pusface.
Did you make these?
Seriously, do you have to be
such a dick?
Yup. And seriously,
do you have to smell like a sewer?
Um, no, that's just your face.
Sorry? Groin juice? Urgh!
No!Adam!
JONNY HOWLS
It's actually 6.554 miles.
Oh!
So, we only got you a couple of
things,
cos you only asked for a
couple of things.
The world's most boring
Here. Is this a present?
No, it's your arse.
Course it's a present!
No need to say thank you.
It's a battery tester.
Yes.
Well, say thank you.
In a minute! I haven't tested it
yet.
You're going to test the battery
tester? Obviously.
God, how much crap
do you keep in your pockets?
Pillock. Here! Have a pound!
Ow! God, Dad!Martin!
LAUGHS
Nice shot, Dad.
TESTER BEEPS
It works.
You're welcome.
PHONE RINGS
Oh, please stop calling me.
SIGHS
It's your wretched mother
again.
SIGHS
It's your wretched mother
again.
Ugh! Horrible Grandma.
Hello again, Cynthia.
It's Martin's birthday.
I know, Cynthia.
Martin's my only son.
Cynthia, we've had this conversation
three times already.
We're having a quiet night in,
just the four of us, OK?
She hung up. Again. Good.
Nice one, Mum.
I'm sorry, but I'm not having
that grotty old moose ruining
another of Dad's birthdays.
Yes, another
of Dad's wonderful birthdays.
Huh?
Here, Mr Wonderful.
Is that my other present?
No, it's your other arse.
Drill bits. You're welcome again.
Where are you going?
Well, to test the drill
bits, obviously.
CHUCKLES
What is wrong with him tonight?
Maybe we could drill
into his head to find out.
DRILLING
Dad!Right!
I'm not having any more of this
crap!
My drill!
Martin! It's your birthday!
Why are you being such a grumpy git
the whole time?
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
What is going on? What?
Nothing is going on.
TUTS
Dad? Dad?
HE SIGHS
All right! God.
I'm not going into space.
I'm sorry?
I'm not going into bloody space!
Wha...?
You're not going into space?
When are you not going into space?
Tonight?
Well, obviously not tonight!
Did you see my spaceship outside?
Er, have you been drinking?
Yeah, out of the drains?
What are you talking about, Martin?
I read an article.
Right.
Read it.
What? The whole article?
Oh, bleeding hell!
"Affordable space travel for all
"not expected until 2050, say
experts."
And?
2050.
And? Well, I'll be dead
by then, won't I?
Will you? Yes.
Right, and who told you that?
Your psychic doctor?
Prats. The computer system.
It's called the internet,
but do go on.
There was this programme on
it, and it asks your date of birth
and other stuff, and then it tells
you when you're going to,
you know, die.
Oh, Martin. Why would you do that?
I die on April 9th, 2048.
Oh, my God, Dad!
I did yours as well.
No way! What?
You did the boys?
Er, we really don't want to know
when we die, thank you! Yeah!
You looked up when our lovely
sons are going to...
...perish? What?
How could you do such a thing?
You didn't do mine, did you?
Well, you last a couple of months
after me.
Oh, my God! Incredible.
3rd of June, 2048.
Dad!Martin! Right.
Thank you for telling me
when I'm actually going to die.
Thank you so much!
You're unbelievable!
Eh? Calm down, Jackie.
It's probably not the
exact exact date.
Just go away. Although, it's
probably pretty close,
because I did have to put in quite a
lot of your medical data so, er...
Right. Thank you again!
DOORBELL
SIGHS
If that's your bloody mother
coming to ruin everything...
I am so angry with you!
Well done.
Yes, good work, Doctor Death.
Please don't be her.
GROANS
Jackie?
Oh, Jim! Thank God it's you.
Oh, Jackie, thank God it's you, too.
Um, can I help you, Jim?
What?
Oh, yes, we just popped round
to wish Martin a happy birthday,
didn't we, Milson?
Um, hello, Jim.
Happy birthday, Martin.
Balls!Ugh!
Um, Jim, could I have your date of
birth, please?
OTHERS: Do not tell him!
Don't tell him that!
Right, why don't you go in there
and practise holding your breath
for an hour, hmm?
Jackie!
Bye-bye, Martin.
But, Jackie!
Anything else, Jim? Yes, um,
I wondered if I could perhaps
perform some magic tricks
for the birthday boy.
What? Magic tricks?
You do magic?
Oh, yes, we've been teaching
ourselves
lots of magic tricks lately,
haven't we, Milson?
Look.
NERVY MUTTERINGS
What are you doing?
Magic with my magic hankie.
Does Martin enjoy magic?
Absolutely hates it.
Would rather set his head on fire.
Um, do come in, Jim.
Any card? Any card, Martin.
Bleeding hell. Now what?
Look at the card.
And now tell me what the card is.
Really? Um, the Four Of Clubs.
BREATHES HEAVILY
Martin Goodman,
is your card the King Of Diamonds?
What?
No. The Four Of Clubs!
Oh, yes. I can never do that one.
Well, thanks so much, Jim.
Er, sorry, Martin, but I don't think
Jim's quite finished. Have you?
Oh, no, Jackie,
I've got lots more magic for Martin.
How exciting!
Do carry on, Jim. Yes, bravo!
Bravo! Buggers.
Well, that's your dad sorted
for the night!
Maybe Jim will saw him in half.
CHUCKLES
Or much smaller pieces.
Shall we just start dinner without
him? Yes, please! Definitely.
Right. Birthday beef
without the birthday boy!
# Skill McGill! #
# Skilligan McGilligan! #
DOOR CLOSES
Huh? Hello?
What are you doing? Where's Jim?
He's gone.Gone?
Yeah, I paid him and he went.
You paid him? Ah!
So that's how you get rid of Jim.
What did you pay him with?
I found 20 quid in your purse.
Fantastic.
Er, thank you very much, Martin.
Can I have my dinner now?
No, you cannot have your dinner now.
Boys?
Jackie! What am I going to bleeding
eat? It's my birthday!
Er, really? I thought it
was your death day.
Not this crap again.Well, maybe we
don't want our dinner
with someone who keeps telling
us when we're gonna drop dead.
What?
with someone who keeps telling
us when we're gonna drop dead.
What?
I didn't tell you when the boys were
going to drop dead. How kind.
Anyway, those two have nothing
to worry about.
They go on for years.
Please shut up.
Yes, shut up, Martin. Oh, potatoes.
You last right up to
the Mars Colonisation Programme.
Um, and what year is
the Mars Colonisation Programme?
Er...
2085.
GROANS
Wait! 2085 that's all right,
isn't it?
GROANS
Wait! 2085 that's all right,
isn't it?
GROANS
Wait! 2085 that's all right,
isn't it?
Er, yeah, actually,
that is ages away.
See? And you get to go to Mars,
you lucky sods.
What do you think about that?
Yeah, that's pretty cool. Yeah.
Sorry, no. Adam, you
get to go to Mars.
Jonny, you don't. What?
Cos you die first.
Ah! I die first?
But Adam's older than me!
Yeah, but he lives longer cos of
his, you know, running and exercise.
Of course! My running and exercise.
HE HEAVES
July 22nd, 2082.
That's when you die.
Oh, my God!What?
Dad just told me my death day.
Oh, Martin! Ow!
July 22nd, 2082.
Don't tell me, Jonny!
Ow!
Jackie, calm down. Adam's gonna go
to Mars. Isn't that fantastic?
That is fantastic.
I need a drink.
But, Jackie, Mars!
Don't you think that's incredible?
Mars, Mars, Mars.
Brilliant. Well, I promise
I'll give you a lovely funeral.
Thank you. And I'll try not
to fart on your grave.
Pusface!
Anyway, it's all crap, isn't it,
working out when you're gonna die?
Yeah. It's just a shame
you never took up running.
Right, well, I'll just start running
now, then I'll live longer than you.
You're gonna start running now, are
you? Yeah. Let's go for a run.
Sorry? You want to go for a run
right now?
Yes, I can run as far as you, easy!
Where are you going?
Putting my shoes on.
Pissface? Your mother!
What?
Oh.Yeah.
Go on, then.
March 20th, 2085.
Great.
You're running now? Now?
Yes!You can't run now.
We've got beef.
Can you move out of the way,
please?Jonny!
Yes, he has gone insane.
Right. Ready, Pusface?
Wait. That's not...
Oh, my God.
Horrible Grandma.
Happy birthday, Martin.
Balls!
Banning me from seeing my son
on his birthday...
I wasn't banning you, Cynthia.
My only son.
I don't think we got your card
this year, did we, Martin?
Jackie. That's because I didn't send
a card.
Fair enough.
Oh, I thought you were going
to give Martin a present then.
Bleeding hell, Jackie.
Why would I give Martin a present?
His birthday, perhaps?
But he's not a baby.
Um, that's not quite how birthdays
work...
Horrible.....Grandma.
I stopped giving Martin presents
years ago when he was seven.
Six. Yes, six.
I remember, because I just
re-wrapped the same present
I'd given him when he was five.
SHE LAUGHS
Lovely. A whistle.
Lovely.
Well, he wasn't to know, was he?
Jackie, can we bloody eat now?
All right!
I'm looking forward to the beef.
Oh, are you, Cynthia?
Well, it's about the only thing you
make that's edible.
Get rid of her?
How am I going to get rid of her?
Er, poison?
Garrotting? Drowning in a bucket!
Any of those will do. Idiots.
I really don't care
how you get rid of her, Martin.
You can take her to Mars
in your spaceship if you like.
Jackie, I don't have a spaceship!
Ju... OK.
Let's all just sit down,
eat our beef and...
Eat our beef?! I am not eating
my lovely beef with that... woman!
But, Jackie...And instead of
looking up
when your wife and kids drop dead,
why don't you look up when your pig
of a mother snuffs it?!
Er, yes, actually!
Who the hell do you think
I looked up first?!
And? She lives to
a shitting hundred.
Of course she does.What?!
OK, if you're not going to get
rid of her,
you can have your dinner with her.
Huh?
Jacqueline, are you going to feed me
tonight or what?
Oh, yes, Cynthia.
And? Grim.
Really? How grim?
Prison grim. Ooh, that is grim.
Well, he wanted a shitty birthday,
so...
To Dad's shitty birthday!
OTHERS: Dad's shitty birthday!
Uh...
Er, no, you're not allowed in here!
What? Please don't send me back in
there.
Martin, go and sit with your mother!
But, Jackie,
I can't take it in there any more.
Any more? You've been in there
for, like, two minutes.
What, that long?!
Oh, hello, Mum.
There's been a little accident.
It's all over them!
Yes, I don't know how it happened.
I must have just slipped and
somehow bumped into the bottle.
It's on the walls as well!
Yes, it is, isn't it?
And this wall?
You did this on purpose,
didn't you, Cynthia?
I beg your pardon? Oh, God.
You know, Cynthia, you come here
and you treat this place like crap.
Oh, do I, Jacqueline?
Yes, you bloody do!
Well, maybe that's because this
place IS crap.
Er...This place is crap, is it?
Yes. Crap.
And the food.Really?
I thought you liked my beef -
you said it was "edible".
Well, I was wrong.
It was inedible.
Sort of see that one coming.
And you know what else is crap?
No, do tell me.
Your family.
Your family is crap.
You'd better bloody say something
right now.
Er, Mum...
Have you finished your meal?
Oh, my God! My family's crap?!
Well, I've got news for you,
Cynthia -
you're part of this crap family!
And don't I bloody know it?!
With my crap daughter-in-law
and her crap hair!
WHISPERS: Crap hair?!
And those idiotic boys,
whose names I can barely
be bothered to remember.
I'm Nicholas. And I'm Lawrence.
And your son? Eh, Cynthia?
What about your son? Your only son?
Well, he used to be bearable,
but then he met you.
Right!
Martin?
I'm not taking this shit any more!
You, Cynthia Goodman,
are a terrible mother!
Hooray!
And a terrible human being!
Hoorah!
Oh, it's all coming out now!
Well, don't think I don't know
your secret name for me.
It's Horrible Grandma, isn't it?
Yup! It's Horrible Grandma!
Cos you're the most horrible grandma
in the world.
JACKIE: Er, universe.
Multiverse.Huh?
Well, cos scientists think there
could be
any number of universes out there.
Yeah, maybe later.
Well, since you all hate me so
much...
And we do.
You're going home and never coming
back? No.
I'm going to stay right here
and you'll never get rid of me!
SHE GIGGLES
You're a pig!
Well, you would know!
DOOR SLAMS
Oh, my God.
What just happened?
More gin. More gin!
GLASS SMASHES
What the...?
Huh?
Oh, dear!
The shelves just fell off the wall!
OK, if that cow isn't out of
this bloody house
in two seconds... I just told you
I'm not going anywhere!
Right, then, I'm getting out
of this bloody house!
Jackie...Boys, we're going for a
run.
What?! Mum?
And, Martin? Yes?
You're staying here and guarding
your lunatic of a mother.
Oh, shitting shit!
Careful you don't break
both your legs, Jacqueline.
SHE GROWLS
CYNTHIA GIGGLES
Come on! Best night ever? Possible!
Hello, all!
Oh, God. No, Jim, not now.
Sorry, Jackie, but I think
I left something in your house.
Well, you can get it tomorrow, OK?
Excuse me.
I must have it now, Jackie, I must!
It's my hankie.
Your hankie.
My magic hankie.
I'm sure I left it in here
somewhere.
Please hurry up. Please!
I can't believe you made her tea.
HE SPLUTTERS
It's delicious.
Oh, here it is! Silly me.
It was in my pocket the whole time.
HE SNORTS
What is it?
It's my magic hankie.
Well, bye, all!
MARTIN:Er, goodbye, Jim.
Actually, Jim...
..how would you like to perform
some magic
for my wonderful mother-in-law?
Well, get on with it, you silly man!
Mrs Cynthia Goodman, is your card...
..the ten of hearts?
I just told you, you idiot - it's
the queen of bloody spades!
Oh.
Such a difficult one, isn't it, Jim?
Yes, it's difficult, isn't it?
Perhaps you'd like to see me
make something disappear?
I'd like to see you
make SOMEONE disappear.
Actually, why don't you make me
disappear from this stupid craphole?
Aw, how sweet.
Um, OK, then, Mrs Goodman.
Perhaps I could borrow this towel?
The magic towel?
The magic towel.
And so...
..I say the magic word...
HE STUTTERS:..abadababadababada...
..and she's gone!
Er, isn't she just
sort of behind the towel?
What? Oh, no, no,
she's definitely disappeared.
Right.
And now, with the power of magic,
I will make her come back again.
Please don't.
HE STUTTERS
Cynthia?
As I said,
with such a massive heart attack,
she really wouldn't have
felt a thing, Mr Goodman.
All just very quick and painless.
A good way to go.
Thanks, Doctor.Thank you.
HE EXHALES
Wow.
Yeah.
Again, Martin, I'm so sorry
that I killed your mother...
..with my magic.
Er, right, Jim.
In a way, I did sort of make her
disappear.
Goodbye, Jim. Come on, Milson.
Good girl.
Ooh, and, Martin, here's that 20
back.
Buy yourself something
nice at the funeral.
Er...Goodbye, Jim.
Well, she definitely didn't last to
100.
Adam.
It's all just so strange.
What? Being murdered by magic?
Jonny!
And on my birthday, too.
Yeah, your birthday.
What a birthday.
HE SOBS
Oh, poor Dad.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Dad.
HE CRIES
That's it, Martin.
Aw, let it all out.
SOBBING TURNS TO LAUGHTER
Er...It's just nerves.
Is it nerves?
It's not nerves!
HE LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY
# I change shapes just to hide in
this place
# But I'm still, I'm still an animal
# Nobody knows it but me when I slip
# Yeah, I slip, I'm still an animal